adsluna.com 2019-06-16

# AdsLuna - Advertising Network

**AdsLuna.com** is committed to compliance with the EU General Data Protection Regulation laws and this policy (Privacy and Cookies Policy) sets out our personal information gathering and sharing practices for **AdsLuna.com** (the “ **Websites** ”, “ **Platforms** ”) and the services we provide to Advertisers and Publishers. 

Accordingly with current regulations on the protection of personal data we have improved our privacy policy and procedures to ensure the safety and protection of consumer information. 

**AdsLuna.com** may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are informed on a regular basis.

This Privacy Policy is intended to explain our privacy practices and covers the following areas:

**_1\. Who is Administrator of your personal data_**

The administrator of your personal data is:

**AdsLuna.com**

E-mail: support@adsluna.com

E-mail: support@traffiviews.com

Website: http://adsluna.com

Website: http://trafficviews.com

**_2.  What personal information about you we may collect_**

PUBLISHERS / ADVERTISERS

**By signinig up AdsLuna.com, Trafficviews.pl you give us permission to send sales proposals. If you do not want to be on our e-mailing list, please unsubscribe from it or contact us via e-mail.**

The data we will process for the purposes stated further on in this document is limited to the business contact data related to the company, entity or organization you work for or with whom you collaborate. 

We may collect and process the personal information that you provide us by submitting the registration form on our Websites, subscribing to our newsletters form, perform any other actions on our Websites (Platforms) or by corresponding with us. The information you provide may include your name, address, e-mail address, login to our websites and phone number.

As well, by a user performing any actions on our Websites (Platforms) we may automatically collect the following information:

·       Your **AdsLuna.com, Trafficviews.com** ************ credential information, platform, OS and browser versions, timezone, IP (Internet protocol) and other technical information.

·       Analytical information considering your visits on our Websites (Platforms). This information may include: the incoming source of your visit, your behaviour flow, bounce-rate, enter and exit pages, page response times, certain pages spending time, and other information.

The information we receive from the third-party Information sources (including, for example, business partners, sub-contractors in technical, payment and delivery services, advertising networks, analytics providers, search information providers, credit reference agencies). This document ([Privacy and Cookies Policy](https://www.exoclick.com/privacy-and-cookies-policy/)) **** reflects the occasion of receiving this data. As well, we may notify you when we receive any information about you from the third-parties and the purposes for which we intend to use that data. ****

The processing of personal data, such as the name, address, e-mail address, login to our websites or telephone number of a data subject shall always be in line with the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR), and in accordance with the country-specific data protection regulations applicable to the AdsLuna . 

END-USERS

The data we will process has been obtained through your browsing information archive files, as informed via the cookies policies of the websites of each of our Publishers (websites which show our advertising banners or other ad formats). The data obtained is: URL of the website displaying our ads, referral URL, IP, country, geographical area, browser and operating system.

**_3\. How we may use your personal information_**

PUBLISHERS / ADVERTISERS

The processing of your business contact data relative to maintaining the relationship between **AdsLuna** and you or the company, entity or organization you work for or collaborate with responds to a legitimate interest of our organization, specifically recognized in the privacy regulation.

END-USERS

The processing of your personal data is expressly authorized by the existing regulation. ****

**_4\. How long we will store your data_**

Your personal data will be stored while your relationship with **Ad AdsLuna** **** is ongoing and once said relationship is terminated for whatever cause, unless you oppose to it. Once the relationship is terminated, your data will be processed solely to the effects of demonstrating compliance with the legal or contractual obligations of the Company.

**_5\. What are your rights_**

By accepting of our Privacy Policy and by submitting your information to us, you’re expressing agreement to the processing set out in this document.

We inform you that you have a right to access your personal data, rectify inaccurate data, request its erasure when it is no longer necessary, oppose or limit the processing or request the portability of the data, through the postal and electronic addresses indicated.

####  

#### The right to be informed

You have a right to be aware of our personal data protection clauses and data processing activities, whose details are contained in this document.

####  

#### The right to access your personal data

You have a right to request for information about the personal data we hold about you by sending e-mail to the Administrator: support@adsluna.com . Please state a compelling reason for the request.

####  

#### The right of data correction

You have an option to update your personal data using your profile section. In order to change any additional information please inform us and we will update our data records as soon as possible.

As well, we will take reasonable actions to the data modification to any third parties whom we have passed the same information.

####  

#### The right to data portability

You have a right to receive personal data copy we hold about you. As well, you may request that we transfer your personal data directly to the third party if it’s technically possible.

####  

#### The right to object

If you feel your fundamental rights and freedoms are being impacted you have a right to object us using your personal data, unless we have overriding legitimate grounds for such processing. As well, you have a right to object if we use your personal data for marketing purposes (including profiling) or for statistical and research purposes. Please notify us of your objection and we will cease such data processing.

**_6\. How we protect your personal information_**

**AdsLuna **maintains commercially reasonable physical, electronic and procedural safeguards in order to protect your personal information under the laws and requirements of data protection. Our data servers are protected by security mechanisms and protocols and the personal data stored can only be administered by the designated persons. 

No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security you can contact us at admin@mediacpm.pl

By using the websites **AdsLuna.com, Trafficviews.com** ****[****]() (the Websites) and the services they provide to Advertisers and Publishers (the, “ **You** ”, “ **Your** ”, etc.), you consent to the use of cookies in accordance with this Cookies Policy. The Website uses cookies to distinguish you from other users of the Website. This helps us to provide you with a good experience when you browse the website and also allows us to improve the Website.

**What are cookies and how we use them?**

Cookies are text files containing small amounts of information which are downloaded to your device when you visit a website. Cookies are then sent back to the originating web domain on your subsequent visits to that domain. Most web pages contain elements from multiple web domains so when you visit the Website, your browser may receive cookies from several sources.

Cookies are useful because they allow a website to recognize a user’s device. Cookies allow you to navigate between pages efficiently, remember preferences and generally improve the user experience. They can also be used to tailor advertising to your interests through tracking your browsing across websites.

Session cookies are deleted automatically when you close your browser and persistent cookies remain on your device after the browser is closed (for example to remember your user preferences when you return to the site).

### Performance Cookies

We make use of analytic cookies to analyze how our visitors use our Website and to monitor Website performance. This allows us to provide a high-quality experience by customizing our offering and quickly identifying and fixing any issues that arise. For example, we might use performance cookies to keep track of which pages are most popular, which method of linking between pages is most effective, and to determine why some pages are receiving error messages. We might also use these cookies to highlight articles or site services that we think will be of interest to you based on your usage of the Website. The information collected by these cookies is not associated with your personal information by us or by our contractors.

The Website currently uses the following analytic cookies from **Google Analytics:**

### Session Cookies

These cookie files contain information about how users interact with the Website during the browsing session. This may be information about the frequently visited or most recently visited web pages and about visited sections of the Website, for example, if the user saw an error message.

### Persistent Cookies

These cookies help Website remember information and settings applied by the user, such as language selection, theme selection, menu preferences, internal site bookmarks or favorites, and others. Persistent cookies enable a website to remember you on subsequent visits, speeding up or enhancing your experience of services or functions offered.

##### **Use of IP addresses and weblogs**

We may also use your IP address and browser type to help diagnose problems with our server, to administer our Website and to improve the service we offer to you. An IP address is a numeric code that identifies your computer on the internet. Your IP address might also be used to gather broad demographic information.

We may perform IP lookups to determine which domain you are coming from (e.g. google.com) to more accurately gauge our users’ demographics.

Information from these types of cookies and technologies or about website usage is not combined with information about you from any other source.

###  

### Questions or Comments about this Cookie Policy

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first contact us through email. You can address your general questions and comments by e-mail to support@adsluna.com
